<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>literature on Mike J. O&#39;Brien</title>
    <link>https://mikejobrien.com/categories/literature/</link>
    <description>Recent content in literature on Mike J. O&#39;Brien</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mikejobrien.com/categories/literature/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My 2019 Book List</title>
      <link>https://mikejobrien.com/posts/2019/12-31-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mikejobrien.com/posts/2019/12-31-2019/</guid>
      <description>Books I read in 2019. Rich Dad Poor DadWhat the Rich Teach Their Kids About Money - That the Poor and Middle Class Do Not! By: Robert T. Kiyosaki Liar&amp;rsquo;s PokerRising Through the Wreckage on Wall Street By: Michael Lewis The Ideal Team PlayerHow to Recognize and Cultivate the Three Essential Virtues: A Leadership Fable By: Patrick M. Lencioni The Undoing ProjectA Friendship That Changed Our Minds By: Michael Lewis Atomic HabitsAn Easy &amp;amp; Proven Way to Build Good Habits &amp;amp; Break Bad Ones By: James Clear The 3-Day EffectBy: Florence Williams The Algebra of HappinessNotes on the Pursuit of Success, Love, and Meaning By: Scott Galloway Radical CandorBe a Kick-Ass Boss Without Losing Your Humanity By: Kim Scott The Manager&amp;rsquo;s PathA Guide for Tech Leaders Navigating Growth and Change By: Camille Fournier The ONE ThingThe Surprisingly Simple Truth Behind Extraordinary Results By: Gary Keller, Jay Papasan Accelerate: Building and Scaling High Performing Technology OrganizationsBy: Nicole Forsgren PhD, Jez Humble, Gene Kim FactfulnessTen Reasons We&amp;rsquo;re Wrong About the World - and Why Things Are Better Than You Think By: Hans Rosling, Anna Rosling Rönnlund, Ola Rosling Emotional Intelligence 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 2018 Book List</title>
      <link>https://mikejobrien.com/posts/2018/12-31-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mikejobrien.com/posts/2018/12-31-2018/</guid>
      <description>Books I read in 2018. But What If We&amp;rsquo;re Wrong?Thinking About the Present as If It Were the Past By: Chuck Klosterman The Chaos ImperativeHow Chance and Disruption Increase Innovation, Effectiveness, and Success By: Ori Brafman, Judah Pollack Measure What MattersHow Google, Bono, and the Gates Foundation Rock the World with OKRs By: John Doerr, Larry Page - foreword The UpstartsHow Uber, Airbnb, and the Killer Companies of the New Silicon Valley Are Changing the World By: Brad Stone It Doesn&amp;rsquo;t Have to Be Crazy at WorkBy: Jason Fried, David Heinemeier Hansson QuietThe Power of Introverts in a World That Can&amp;rsquo;t Stop Talking By: Susan Cain Creativity, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 2017 Book List</title>
      <link>https://mikejobrien.com/posts/2017/12-31-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mikejobrien.com/posts/2017/12-31-2017/</guid>
      <description>Books I read in 2017. Never Split the DifferenceNegotiating as if Your Life Depended on It By: Chris Voss Man&amp;rsquo;s Search for MeaningBy: Viktor E. Frankl Start with WhyHow Great Leaders Inspire Everyone to Take Action By: Simon Sinek Leaders Eat LastWhy Some Teams Pull Together and Others Don&amp;rsquo;t By: Simon Sinek Who Moved My Cheese?An Amazing Way to Deal with Change in Your Work and in Your Life By: Spencer Johnson Lead and DisruptHow to Solve the Innovator&amp;rsquo;s Dilemma By: Charles A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 2016 Book List</title>
      <link>https://mikejobrien.com/posts/2016/12-31-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mikejobrien.com/posts/2016/12-31-2016/</guid>
      <description>Books I read in 2016. The Phoenix ProjectA Novel About IT, DevOps, and Helping Your Business Win By: Gene Kim , Kevin Behr , George Spafford The Like SwitchAn Ex-FBI Agent&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Influencing, Attracting, and Winning People Over By: Jack Schafer , Marvin Karlins Team of TeamsNew Rules of Engagement for a Complex World By: General Stanley McChrystal , Tantum Collins , David Silverman , Chris Fussell The Essential Guide for Hiring &amp;amp; Getting HiredPerformance-based Hiring Series By: Lou Adler How to Win Friends &amp;amp; Influence PeopleBy: Dale Carnegie PresenceBringing Your Boldest Self to Your Biggest Challenges By: Amy Cuddy Site Reliability EngineeringHow Google Runs Production Systems By: Betsy Beyer,‎ Chris Jones,‎ Jennifer Petoff,‎ Niall Richard Murphy </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>